<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">Maylians go on the Loose</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Several maylians were seen out and about the landscape</string>
    <string name="article_text">During one of our date days, we sat down and listed all the household tasks that each of us performed; making sure nothing was left out.
        \nComparing Julie’s (seemingly endless) list to mine was a wake-up call that my value of equality in our marriage needed some help. We agreed to split the household jobs and, most important, timeboxed the tasks on our schedules, leaving no doubt about when they would get done.
        \n\nRead more books at www.readmorebooks.com\n\n
        <b><i>Working our way toward a more equitable split of the housework</i></b> restored integrity to my value of equality in my marriage, which also improved the odds of having a long and happy relationship. Lockman’s research supports this benefit: “A growing body of research in family and clinical studies demonstrates that spousal equality promotes marital success and that inequality undermines it.\”
        \nUnlike the other life domains, I don’t need to remind you to make time for work. You probably don’t have much of a choice when it comes to this area. Given that work likely takes up more of your waking hours than any of the other domains, it’s even more important to ensure the time spent there is consistent with your values.
Work can help people live their values of being collaborative, industrious, and persistent. It also allows us to spend time on something meaningful when we labor for someone else’s benefit—like our customers or an important cause. Unfortunately, many of us find that our workday is a hectic mess, plagued by constant interruptions, pointless meetings, and a never-ending flow of emails.
Thankfully, it doesn’t have to be this way.
        \n\n <b><i>We can do more and live better by clarifying our values and expectations with each other at work</i></b>.\nClarification around how we spend our time at work fosters and reinforces the central quality of a positive working relationship: trust.
Every company has its policies. However, when it comes to how employees manage their workloads, many managers have little idea how their colleagues spend their time. Similarly, perhaps the biggest unknown to the employee is how they should spend their time, both inside and outside of work. How responsive should employees be after hours? Are they required to attend happy hours or other events full of “mandatory fun”? Will managers and clients expect employees to fulfill last-minute deadlines? Should they let their spouses know to expect late-night outings when company execs drop into town?
These questions are significant because they directly affect our schedules and, subsequently, the time we have for the other domains in life. A recent survey found 83 percent of working professionals check email after work. The same study notes that two-thirds of respondents take work-related devices, such as laptops or smartphones, with them on vacation. And about half the respondents said they’ve sent work-related emails during meals with family or friends.
Staying late at work or feeling pressured to reply to work-related messages after hours means spending less time with our family and friends or doing something for ourselves. If these demands become more than the employee bargained for, trust and loyalty can erode, along with one’s health and relationships.</string>
</resources>
